[
    {
        "question": "What country does Nigeria share borders within the West?",
        "optionA": "Benin",
        "optionB": "Chad",
        "optionC": "Togo",
        "optionD": "Niger",
        "answer": "Benin"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who of these has NOT been a Senate President?",
        "optionA": "Joseph Wayas",
        "optionB": "Iyorchia Ayu",
        "optionC": "Adolphus Wabara",
        "optionD": "Arthur Nzeribe",
        "answer": "Arthur Nzeribe"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who is Nigeriaâ€™s Minister of Education?",
        "optionA": " Adamu Adamu",
        "optionB": "Aja Nwachukwu",
        "optionC": "Ruqqayat Rufai",
        "optionD": "Mallam Ibrahim Shekarau ",
        "answer": "Adamu Adamu"
    },

    {
        "question": "what state is the great Onitsha market located?",
        "optionA": "Abia",
        "optionB": "Imo",
        "optionC": "Anambra",
        "optionD": "Enugu",
        "answer": "Anambra"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which Two state was formerly known as BENDEL state",
        "optionA": "Delta and Bayelsa",
        "optionB": "Edo and Ondo",
        "optionC": "Benue and Kogi",
        "optionD": "Edo and Delta",
        "answer": "Edo and Delta"
    },

    {
        "question": "What does the two supporting horses in the nigeria coat of arm represent",
        "optionA": "Strength",
        "optionB": "Dignity",
        "optionC": "Loyalty",
        "optionD": "Support",
        "answer": "Dignity"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which African country first gained independence?",
        "optionA": "Nigeria",
        "optionB": "South Africa",
        "optionC": "Liberia",
        "optionD": "Ethopia",
        "answer": "Liberia"
    },

    {
        "question": "How many ethnic groups do we have in Nigeria?",
        "optionA": "774",
        "optionB": "365",
        "optionC": "205",
        "optionD": "250",
        "answer": "250"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who is the current chief of justices of Nigeria?",
        "optionA": "Arthur Nzeribe",
        "optionB": "Joseph Wayas",
        "optionC": "Ibrahim Tanko Muhammad",
        "optionD": "Adolphus Wabara",
        "answer": "Ibrahim Tanko Muhammad"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of these is a suburb of Lagos?",
        "optionA": "Victoria Garden City",
        "optionB": "Ikpoba Slope",
        "optionC": "Independence Layout",
        "optionD": "Asokoro District",
        "answer": "Victoria Garden City"
    },

    {
        "question": "11. Which of these languages is spoken in Delta state?",
        "optionA": "Birom",
        "optionB": "Isoko",
        "optionC": "Esan",
        "optionD": "Nupe",
        "answer": "Isoko"
    },

    {
        "question": "The Nigeria House of Representatives has how many members ",
        "optionA": "774",
        "optionB": "360",
        "optionC": "109",
        "optionD": "469",
        "answer": "360"
    },

    {
        "question": "Where is Abubakar Tafawa Balewa University?",
        "optionA": "Lagos",
        "optionB": "Bauchi",
        "optionC": "Yola",
        "optionD": "Abuja",
        "answer": "Bauchi"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of these is NOT a bridge across the Lagos Lagoon?",
        "optionA": "Ikeja Bridge",
        "optionB": "Eko Bridge",
        "optionC": "Carter Bridge",
        "optionD": "Third Mainland Bridge",
        "answer": "Ikeja Bridge"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who was the president of 'Kalakuta Republic'?",
        "optionA": "Tai Solarin",
        "optionB": "Uche Onwubuya",
        "optionC": "Fela Anikulapo-Kuti",
        "optionD": "Gani Fawehinmi",
        "answer": "Fela Anikulapo-Kuti"
    }
]